Sanya Prokhorov
Саня Прохоров
and the rest are serving somewhere now they are conducting a
а остальные ж где-то сейчас служат они
service you understand They are soulful
службу ведут понимаешь Они душевно
in rough Yes but they are now bringing light to
начерно Да но они несут теперь свет
people how do you understand
людям как это понимаешь
how horror horror
как ужас ужас
horror Hello
ужас Привет
Hello me Jor it's almost the same to
Здравствуйте меня джор это почти тоже
them But I
самое им Но меня
understood where you are from Georgy I see you are a
понял вы откуда Георгий Я вижу вы
Christian North Caucasus And you are a priest
христианин Северный Кавказ А вы батюшка
I see you are a Christian you have a book of
Я вижу вы христианин у вас книга есть
Christ Yes show me Yes God
Христова Да покажите Да Боже
Christianity you are
христианство вы
Orthodox Yes And you I am also Orthodox
православный Да А вы Я тоже православный
Romanian Orthodox Church And
румынская православная церковь А вы к
what denomination do you belong to Well Russian
какой относитесь деноминации Ну Русская
Orthodox Church in Ossetia
православная церковь в Осетии
or where are you then look at us in the
или где вы значит смотрите у нас на
Caucasus Well all this is included in the
Кавказе Ну это самое всё входит в
Russian Orthodox
русскую православную
Church Well that's how it would be And where
церковь Ну вот как бы так вот А где
exactly are you in the North
именно вы на Северном
Caucasus Stavropol Krai but I study
Кавказе Ставропольский край но изучаю
history The history of Christianity in the North
историю Историю христианства на Северном
Caucasus let's
Кавказе вот
say Alania so yeah that's how it would be this is
Алания скажем так вот да как бы вот это
part well that's how it would be well the Caucasus and we have
часть ну как бы это ну Кавказ да и у нас
preserved the most ancient temples
сохранились древнейшие храмы
which date from the 6th to the 10th century so
который датируется с VI по X век так и
now I will show you the most ancient temple
вот сейчас я вам покажу древнейший храм
It's really small Well, there used to be a
Он правда маленький Ну раньше была
house church, as it were, this is the
домовая церковь как бы оно это самое вот
most ancient temple in Russia
самый древний храм в России
operating in the 10th
действующей X
century And what about all the temples in
века А как же всякие храмы в
Novgorod, they were a little later The fact is
Новгороде они были немножко позже Дело в
that Alania adopted Baptism 100
том что Алания приняла Крещение на 100
years earlier, this is in the 10th century, in
лет раньше это де век в X веке уже в
Kyiv there was already a church of the
Киеве церковь была
Tithes I know I know But for 100
Десятинная Я знаю Я знаю Вот но на 100
years for 100 years I'm saying that from now until the 10th
лет на 100 лет Я же говорю что с се по X
century,
век сохранились
temples have survived, for example, the Temple on Mount Shuana is
храмы вот допустим Храм на горе Шуана
super, let's say what's your name, Georgy,
супер давайте как вас зовут ещ Георгий
yes, yes, gg, let's do a prayerful
да да гги давайте сделаем молитвенное
silence for 30 seconds In the name of all the
молчание 30 секунд Во имя всех
temples Let them bless all the
храмов Пусть благословят все
temples,
храмы
super By the way, of the modern temples in the
супер кстати из современных храмов на
Caucasus, are only mosques opening now,
Кавказе сейчас открываются или только
on average, two or three temples a year, according to the
в среднем по по два-три храма в год по
D-T temple per year Are you a parishioner of which
д-т храма в год Вы прихожанин какого
temple, a large cathedral? Where is the large
храма большого собора А где большой
cathedral in Vladikavkaz The Temple of St. George
собор во Владикавказе Храм Георгия
the Victorious, you are
Победоносца вы
not Ossetian I am Russian but I just live there
осетин нет Я русский но живу просто там
How did you end up in
А как вы попали на во
Vladikavkaz My parents live here,
Владикавказ У меня родители здесь живут
you  sko years
вам ско лет
33 33 for me 43 I'm a little older Yes I'm dumb
33 33 по мне 43 Я немножко старше Да я
And you're
нем А вы паломничество
making a pilgrimage Yes I was in Jerusalem when you
совершаете Да я был в Иерусалиме когда
were in the seventeenth year on the Wailing Wall were
были в семнадцатом году на стене плача
nearby was in the
были рядышком
Jordan were in the river were given
был в Иордане были в реке
ov took washed given
давались ове принимали омывали давался
super How do you
супер Как у ва
feel
ощущения
great I'll say So here in the
здоровские я скажу Так у нас в
European part Eh like not quite
европейской части Ээ как не совсем не
such rivers as the Jordan Jordan has
такие реки как Иордан Иордан имеет
some kind of energy Despite the fact
какую-то такую энергетику Несмотря на то
that it's so yellow Swampy
что она вот такая жёлтая Заболоченная
muddy Yes here in Moldova I would never
мутная Да вот я бы у нас в Молдове в
go into such a river I
такую речку не зашёл бы ни за что я
thought there I don't know there are
подумал там не знаю там черви водятся
some kind of worms there And toads in And here well this is
какие-то Да и жабы во А тут ну это
holy yes you dive in and you get out and there's a
святаго да ты окунается и ты выходишь и
line this line you want to
очередь вот эта очередь ты хочешь
enjoy and they tell you Come on come on get
насладиться а тебе говорят Давай давай
out because there are these machine cheats Yes
вылазь потому что и автомат читы эти
you also have Yes yes yes on the border
стоят Да тоже у тебя Да да да на границе
yes yes yes So yes Well well the spirit The
дадада да Так что да Ну ну дух Дух
Holy Spirit is felt like that and when you get out
Святой так ощущается и ты когда выходишь
of this water there is such a feeling that  you got into
из этой воды такое ощущение что ты попал
another world just like in another dimension all
в иной мир прямо как вот вдго измерение
the dirt all this
с тебя просто вся грязь вся вот это
layering you know this everyday life All this
наслоение знаешь вот это бытовой Вот это
negativity all the sins somehow washed away
всё негатив все грехи как-то смылись
right I had such a feeling And you have the same thing the same thing
прямо у меня такое было ощущение А у вас
And excuse me please who are you
то же самое то же самое А извините
by education I
пожалуйста вы кто по образованию я
look I have a secular education
смотрите у меня есть мирское образование
and a church education
и церковное образование
I studied at the theological seminary Yes but
Я учился в духовной семинарии Да но к
unfortunately I did not finish it I was kicked out
сожалению я её не закончил меня выгнали
of the theological seminary I had well like a
из духовной семинарии у меня был ну как
sin I
бы грешок
understand Well I graduated from the seminary I graduated from the
понял Ну я окончил семинарию Я окончил
seminary And where did you graduate from
семинарию А где вы заканчивали
Stavropol and You know there is such a song
ставропольскую а Знаете есть такая песня
about the seminary Well probably
про семинарию Ну наверное вам
familiar to you in the
знакомая у
seminary garden our father inspector
семинарскому саду отец инспектор наш
walking home pinot I came to me TD with
гуляв до дому пино Я пришёл ан мене ТД с
caught father inspector I am your son Forgive
поймал отец инспектор я ваш сын Прости
me move once and I will not sin dubiv
мене ход раз один и я не буду дубив
but go to prayer at one o'clock you have
грешить та на молитву в час ходить ты
good intentions sleep and you sin also not the media but
намер добрый сну и ты греши теж не СМИ а
for peace of
для спокойствия
mind
душине
write a paper father inspector you are a monk And I in the
напиши отец инспектор вы монах А я у
jacket in the pants require Mashka  find Yes on
кители в штанах требо Машку найти Да на
pafi iti What
пафи ити Это на каком
language is Ukrainian I don't know we don't have
языке украинский А я не знаю у нас в
this language in Moldova and where did you
Молдове нету этого языка а вы где его
study it now at po And where did you study
изучали сейчас у по А где вы изучали
this
этот
language I know I just understood it a little I do
язык Я знаю просто его немножко
n't we don't have
понял я я не у нас в Молдове нет
Ukrainian language in Moldova so I hear that it's
украинского языка поэтому я слышу что
some kind of Slavic but I didn't
какой-то вроде как Славянский но не
think It doesn't look like Slavic at all Well that's how it is yes
подумал На на славянс вообще не
yes I understood Well
похож Ну вот так вот да да понял Ну у
you have a coat of arms it's Cheburashka with a
вас же вон герб это само Чебурашка с
Ukrainian coat of arms not that look this
гербом украинским не это смотрите это
coat of arms my friends from Ukraine sent me
герб это мне друзья из Украины прислали
but I don't understand the language
но я язык не понимаю
at all I understand Do you have a wife
вообще понятно А у вас жена есть
Georgy not
Георгий нету
yet I mean are you divorced or not yet not yet
пока В смысле вы развелись или ещ не
but a small question you know that you ca
а маленький вопрос вы же знаете что
n't commit adultery well before marriage I know I studied economic law
нельзя знаю я экономическое право
no masturbation is
изучал нет рукоблудие
serious no no no and you can't
серьёз нет нет нет и с Девой не слега
eat with a Virgo Not with any Virgo or with an old woman no No
ешь Ни с какой ни с Девой ни с старой
No with a
нет Нет Нет с
husband I don't understand Well with someone you are a
мужем не понял Ну с кем-то ж вы
slyadneva because I slept with a girl
сляднева потому что я с девчонкой
A  why didn't you
переспал А почему не
get married as if she was the
женились как бы она была
daughter of Proto Ere
дочка прото эре
Yes, I understand,
Да понятно
she's so pretty When she was watering a flowerbed at our
такая симпатичная Она когда клумбу у нас
seminary, everyone would come out and
там в семинарии поливала все выходили
look at her
так смотрели у неё такое
dress, a little bit of a non-canonical length,
платьишко немножко не канонической длины
I would say And I understand Well, how would I go to
я бы сказал и Понятно ну как бы я пошёл
help
как-то помогать
her in the garden and
ей по саду и
Georgy, we communicate so normally I'm just
Георгий так нормально общаемся я просто
all sorts of drunk here Yes, and with you at least it's
тут всякая это пьяная Да а с тобой хоть
possible Well, on some topics that Well, to my
можно Ну на какие-то такие темы которые
liking, to my liking, I just want to I've
Ну по душе по душе я просто хочу я мало
told this story to few people
кому эту историю рассказывал меня
only some people know me It turns out she
некоторые только знают получается она
seduced me I didn't want her You know
совратила меня я не хотел она вот знаешь
how I learned the biblical story of how
как вот я познал библейский сюжет как
Eve would have
Ева
lived in the Garden of Eden and so would I If it were
жил бы в эдемском саду так и я если бы
n't for
не
Stefania, I would have already graduated from the seminary I would
Стефания я бы уже в семинарии отучился
have a parish now
имел
and she says Come help me Well, I go
и она говорит Пошли мне поможешь Ну я
without a second thought We go in there there is a
без задней мысли иду Мы заходим там
utility room where there are
такое есть подсобное помещение где
tools for the garden Yeah And there
инструментарий для сада Угу И там такой
is a small sofa there she and my mother
диванчик есть небольшой она и матушкой
usually rested there after working in the garden
отдыхал там обычно после работы в саду
She says Sit down Well, I sat down I'm sitting
Она говорит Присядь Ну я присел сижу
Well, I look Well, she's a Virgo, so
похо Ну и смотрю Ну она Дева такая ну
she's got a dress in it Yes, below the knees, of course,
она платье в неё Да ниже колен конечно
yes But not much below the knees, I would say, and
да Но не сильно ниже колен я бы сказал и
she's walking, spinning, Yes, here she's
она ходит что-то крутится Да тут
setting up this inventory, bending over, and
расставляет этот инвентарь нагина ется и
listening to me, to my sin, I'm not Dus' I
слушает меня на грех я не Дусь у меня я
still sort of studied a little at the seminary
всё-таки как бы в семинарии немножко
and then she just unexpectedly comes up
проучился и тут она просто неожиданно
and sits on my
она подходит и садится мне на
feet I Georgy, I'll tell you, I've never
ноги я Георгий скажу я в жизни не
experienced such a thrill in my life, I was
испытывал такого трепета душевно я
confused, I was like
растерялся я вот
that at first I didn't understand what was happening, and
так я сначала не понял что происходит а
she grabs my shoulders and starts
она хватает мои плечи и начинает меня
kissing me
целовать
Well, and then, why didn't we get married, it
Ну а дальше бе пому не женились надо
was necessary, like, well, to continue this very thing, and that's
было как бы ну это самое продолжить да и
it, as I continued, I continued,
всё как я продолжил я продолжил мы
so we continued, but then Her
так так продолжили но потом зашёл Её
father came in It's clear, uh, here the question was no longer
отец Понятно ээ тут уже был вопрос не
about getting married, but the question was about
про то чтобы жениться а вопрос про том
how to get out of this alive, he's very much a convoy,
как это живым выйти из этой он очень
I've never heard in my life that he caught it so
обоз он я в жизни не слышал чтобы он так
badly,
скверно словил
of course, he urges after every
он конечно квести так после каждого
swear word,
брано слова
but I understood that Stefania Let's say I'm not the
но я так понял что Стефания Скажем я не
first one she's seduced, that's why
первый кого она совратила поэтому потому
that he spoke so unflatteringly to her well he
что он так нелестно к ней отзывался
says I will not call this word with the
говорит не буду называть это слово на
letter B
букву Б
And he told her you will be
И сказал ей будешь
locked up for a week And I told you
заперто неделю седмицу А мне сказал
I was very angry with you
я на тебя гнева сильно
But by the evening so that you were not here
Но к вечеру чтобы тебя тут не
understandably sad sad sad
было понятно печально печально
la Wait wait I had another time with us
ла Подожди подожди я ещ разу у нас был
in the seminary my friend Sanya
ещё в семинарии друг мой Саня
Prokhorov is very religious himself from the same source he
Прохоров очень набожный сам родом тоже
came to Moldova with his parents he
он он в Молдову приехал с родителями он
himself is from the Vologda region somewhere Russian
сам из Вологодской области где-то руский
also a Russian
тоже русский
guy he has a more interesting story Well how
парень у него интереснее история Ну как
can you say it sadder
печальнее можно сказать
his
его
hieromonk there it turns out Yes when
иеромонах там оказывается Да мне когда
Sanya then already go you don't tell me no It turns
Саня потом уже го не рассказываете не
out this it turns out this was
Оказывается это оказывается это было
repeatedly yes that is, his from the first
неоднократно да то есть его с первого
year And he was such a nice boy
курса А он такой симпатичный мальчик был
yes and this and in novels And he is so fat I
да и этот и романах А он такой толстый Я
never thought never yva Well
никогда не подумал никогда не ыва Ну и
wait well I'll share It's just that maybe you
подожди ну поделюсь Просто может у вас в
also had this in seminaries well it was we didn't have this
семинариях тоже было такое ну было у нас
we didn't have this Well
такого не было у нас такого не было Ну
someone
кого-то
hieromonk
иеромонах
No seriously no talk I also for now Sanya
Нет серьёзно говор нет Я тоже пока Саня
Prokhorov didn't tell Yes, while he
Прохоров не рассказал Да пока он
was hanging himself He wanted to hang himself I
повеситься Хотел хотел повеситься я
see he's pulling the noose I Hello Sanya What is it
смотрю он петлю тянет я Алло Санёк Что
he told me And this
такое он мне рассказал Вот и этот
fat one he is 150 kg hieromonk so fat
толстый он 150 кг иеромонах такой жирный
In short, he also got a cross and he
Короче у него ещё крест стал да и он
took it with his fingers by di Sanya
своими перстами брал его за ди Саню
Prokhorov took it by Yes he pressed him to the
Прохорова брал за Да прижимал его к
wall and inserted his own into him This is a
стенке и вводил в него своё Вот это
swearing place and Horror horror This is horror
бранное место и Ужас ужас Это ужас
just horror this is blasphemy such a sin sodomy and
просто ужас это богохульство такое грех
against the will of the
мужеложество причём против воли
novice
послушника
and Sanya was afraid afraid Tell us Well,
и Саня боялся боялся Сказать нам Ну
because you understand yes that everyone would
потому что ты же понимаешь да что все
kind of
как бы
laugh at that well in short
засмеют вот ну короче
Sanya then I talked him out of it he remembered after a
Саня тогда я его отговорил он через
month So wait I'll tell you
месяц пом Так подожди я Ну расскажу
later the
потом приехала
diocesan commission arrived it turned out that well they had
комиссия епархиальная оказалось что ну
conversations with the novice it turned out
провели беседы с послушника оказалось
that this situation is not the only one and in the
что эта ситуация не одна и
novels He about 10 boys where
романах Он около 10 мальчиков де
boys another seminary graduate arrived
мальчиков приехал ещё выпускник
one Father Anthony he gave testimony
один отец Антоний вот он дал показания
that when he studied at the seminary also and in the
что когда он учился в семинарии тоже и
novels this one was
романах этот
inclined to that  forced
склонялся то заставил
him to satisfy this hieromonk in a way
его способом удовлетворить этого
It's just awful and I, well, let's
иеромонаха Это просто ужас это и я я ну
say Sanya Prokhorov
скажем ю Саня Прохоров
and the rest are serving now they are conducting a service you
а остальные сейчас служат они службу
understand They are soulfully in
ведут понимаешь Они душевно
rough They are now bringing light to people how do you
начерно Они несут теперь свет людям как
understand
это понимаешь
how Yes, awful, awful, awful, la Wait, damn You
как Да ужас ужас ужас ла Подожди блин Ты
eat so well
так классно кушаешь прямо аж аппетит
I see that your appetite has woken up Yes
смотрю у тебя так проснулся
Listen, and you Well, was it there Well, the guy
Да Слушай а у вас Ну было там Ну парне
masturbation is
рукоблудие в
not in this well and how did they satisfy themselves
этом нет ну а как они удовлетворяли себя
with girls how can't you do that with
с девочками как с девочками так нельзя с
girls
девочками
either no So then they got married The
тоже нет Так они потом женились
only thing is that only one said that he would
Единственное что один только сказал что
n't get
не
married that's how it was like that She
женится вот как бы так так Она его
met him later, and on another day and kicked him in the
встретила потом причём в другой день и с
balls Change the expression and gave him a kick in the balls and what kind
ноги Измени выражение по яйцам дала а
of girl was she Where was she from I do
что что за девочка была Откуда это
n't know where she was from it was
была Я не знаю откуда она это было
just in the fall he got all dressed up and was walking she came up to
просто осенью
him and started talking and she
нему подошла начали общаться и она ему с
kicked him in the balls like everything was
ноги по яйцам заехала как бы всё
cool And why didn't you mess around with girls
прикольно А ты почему с девочками не
I talked but didn't sleep And how did you
мутил я общался но не спал А а как это
talk but didn't  slept I'm interested I
общался но не спал Мне же интересно я
usually If I talked
обычно Если общался уже
then no no no I didn't sleep as if it
потом не не не я не спал как бы до этого
just didn't get to that we broke up in the World Cup and
просто не доходило расставались в ЧМ а
what it got to I
до чего
say Well okay And
доходило не доходило говорю Ну хорошо А
at what stage did you Well at least
на каком этапе вы Ну хотя бы
kiss Well at least like that
целовались Ну хотя вот так вот
touched Okay I won't tell
трогал Ладно не буду рассказывать
Tell me
Расскажи
please how he started eating in
пожалуйста как он начал жрать в
days so he started to eat away stress Damn I almost
дня так стресс заедать начал Блин я чуть
squeezed
не зажал
not a
не
story Nera And his eyes are so short they
рассказ Нера А глаза аж такие короче
glow This is a bomb
светятся Это бомба
video the guy wanted to tell him about the temples there what kind of ones he
ролик чувак про храмы хотел там какие
has And here he tells him the reality of his
там у него во А тут ему реали его
seminary let's
семинарии
go get a normal
рассказать пошли нормального
interlocutor to you God sent a normal
собеседника тебе Бог послал нормального
interlocutor scream
собеседника ора
Yes I had a Moldovan flag I'm from Moldova
Да у меня был флаг Молдовы Я из Молдовы
just today I
просто сегодня я в честь
hung up a
Великобритании повесил себе флаг
UK flag in honor of Great Britain I had a call with my partners
Великобритании у меня с моими партнёрами
from Great Britain Got it That's
из Великобритании был
good What are you
созвон Понятненько Это хорошо О чём
talking about today
сегодня общаешься
listen I forgot to ask yesterday What
слушай я вчера Забыл спросить Какие
icons do you have you showed me no
иконы У тебя есть ты мне показывал ни
icons I won't get up now and
кае иконы есть Я сейчас пока не встану а
why Well now my leg hurts a little
почему Ну сейчас у меня немножко нога
that's why  lay down What happened to my
болит я поэтому прилёг Что случилось с
leg I have arthrosis God Let's pray to
ногой у меня артроз Боже Давай помолимся
Saint
святому
Panteleimon Saint Panteleimon send
пантелеймону Святой Пантелеймон пошли
rays of goodness heal us then in the name of the father and the
лучи добра излечи на тогда во имя отца и
son and the holy spirit
сына и святого духа по
I think everything will be
Я думаю что всё будет
fine thank you yes I had Covid and
хорошо спасибо да ковидом переболел и
everything and complications Dava
всё и осложнение Дава
Yes yesterday it was normal today I'm lying there
Да вчера было нормально сегодня вон лежу
almost like this yesterday you were like this well you were like this nominal
почти так вчера ты так ну ты так номинал
pizza Run I remember that Well yes yes yes yes yes you got into a binge you jumped up and
пиццу Бегом я помню что Ну да да да да
ran I didn't understand Where are you running And you
побежал я не понял Куда ты бежишь А ты
ran to the kitchen for
на кухню бежал за
pizza something like that yeah
пиццей типа того да
Listen well that is you don't want to
Слушай а ну то есть ты вообще не хочешь
get up at all to go for an
да вставать чтобы идти за
icon not I'm saying that my leg hurts I've
иконой не я же говорю что нога болит я
only just been lying for about an hour somewhere I'm lying there as
только только уже часок где-то Лежу как
if I don't want it again it will hurt understood Well
бы не хочу опять больно будет понял Ну
watch out otherwise you'll run for pizza again no no no there's
смотри а то снова за пиццей побежишь не
no pizza And what do you have to eat I have
не уже пиццы нету нету А что пожрать
nuts
есть у меня орешки есть
cool Listen are you from Vladikavkaz Yes
прикольно Слушай а ты из Владикавказа Да
myself yes yes what's the most  ancient
сам да да э какой там самый старинный
temple in
храм в самом
Vladikavkaz itself Temple of the Nativity of the
Владикавказе Храм Рождества Божьей
Mother of God Nativity of the Mother of God what
Матери Рождества Божьей матери какого он
century is it the second half of the 19th century even the
века он второй половины 19 века даже
first half of the 10th century And I understood you were just
первый половине X века А понял просто ты
saying that there were temples in Alania even
рассказывал что там в Алании храмы ещё
earlier than in Rus' And this is already this is the 10th
раньше чем на Руси были А это уже это X
century Yes,
век
not in the Caucasus itself in the
Да не в самом воде Кавказе в самом воде
Caucasus itself what I said I understood I understood
Кавказе что я сказал понял понял
yes Listen, and it turns out there is a Russian
да Слушай а там получается Ну Русская
Orthodox Church What kind of diocese do you have?
православная церковь Какая епархия у вас
Caucasian Alanian Alanian diocese
вод Кавказская Аланская Аланская епархия
Yes, that's what it's called Alanian diocese I
Да так и называется Аланская епархия
understood Listen, do you have any female priests
понял Слушай а у вас девушек священников
there are none Well, and you Well, here you are again
нету же так нету Ну а вы Ну вот вы опять
What are you talking about Wait It's just that
О чём вы говорите Подожди Просто у нас
here in Moldova Yes, we have the Moldovan Orthodox
вот в Молдове Да у нас молдов православ
Church here you are in Romania You are in
церковь у нас вы в Румынии Вы же в
Romania well we have it does not have
Румынии ну у нас есть она не имеет
autocephaly Moldovan Orthodox
автокефалию молдов ся православная
Church Yes, and we also
церковь Да вот и у нас
had a decree of the Metropolitan that
ээ было постановление Митрополита что
women are allowed to help the
разрешается женщинам ээ помогать
priests that is, a woman
священним то есть священником ещё пока
cannot be a priest yet Yes, but there
не может быть женщина Да но там паламар
can be a palamar there a woman So maybe for us
может быть ээ женщина Так может быть нам
woman Yes, that's it, there are already three
женщина Да вот это раз есть уже три
women in Moldova who conduct
женщины у нас в Молдове которые ведут
services. That's what helps. Yes, you don't have that. Yes, I
службу Вот это помогают да у вас такого
understand. And
Нет понял А
why? Well, as if there is no need for that yet. There is no need. I
почему Ну как бы пока в этом нету нужды
understand. That's how it is. And by the way, in your
понял вот как-то так А у Вас кстати в
Russian Orthodox Church, a priest
русской православной церкви священнику
can. Zhenya, yes, I understand. And you, you haven't
можно Жени ж так да понял А вы вы Сан не
taken the rank or
приняли или
have taken it. I'm not married yet. Yes, but you haven't
приняли я не женат пока ещё Да но Сан не
taken the rank. I understand. And when are you
принимали священний понял А когда
planning to get
планируете
married? As God wills it. Let's pray
жениться как Бог даст Давайте помолимся
that God will give it to you. Let's do it. Who
чтобы Бог вам дал давайте давайте Кому
needs to
надо
pray to God himself. Let's
молиться самому Богу Давайте
say a prayer. I will support.
вы говорите молитву я буду поддерживать
Lord our God. With a special eye on my
Господи Боже наш ным оком на моё не
unworthiness. George, and bless your
достоинство Георгия и благослови свою
future life. Bride,
дальнейшую жизнь невесту
as God has mercy on you. Glory to the Father
яко милостивы Бога тебе Слава восем отцу
and the Son and the Holy Spirit, now and forever and
и сыну и Святому Духу ныне и присно и во
ever.
веки веков
Amen. And you are the real deal. Which bride can you send?
Аминь А вы заправа именно какую невесту
Because it
потому
may not be the best one.
может не совсем удачную
Well, if it's God's blessing,
послать Ну если это Божье благословение
then everything will be
то всё будет
fine. I understand. I am a believer. And you,
хорошо понял Я человек верующий А вы
your bride. How old do you want her to
себе невесту Сколько лет хотите чтобы ей
be, at least 25?  33 If I'm not
было хотя бы 25 вам 33 Если я не
mistaken yes yes yes well 25 It's a difference
ошибаюсь да да да ну 25 Это разница
how much is there 7 years not 8 years
сколько там 7 лет не 8 лет
normally at least 25 is what you mean
нормально хотя бы 25 это имеете в виду
So that it's already 25 or so that it's not higher than
Чтобы уже было 25 или чтобы было не выше
25 not higher than 25 A I understand I understand that is what
25 не выше 25 А понял понял то есть а
if 26 is already old for you
что если 26 - это уже старенькая для вас
yes Well yes lanko yes Let's
да Ну да ланько да Давай нормально
talk normally if Switch it's a sin to
поговорим если Переключи это грех
switch when two educated
переключать когда два образованных
people are talking or you want to communicate
человека говорят или ты хочешь общаться
not normally normally just a
не нормально нормально просто
phone Now I'm charging Come on let's
телефон Сейчас я на зарядку Давай давай
get on the charger e yes and we'll
став на зарядку е да и будем
talk
говорить
now I'll
сейчас я пока
pray for now I'm just lying here on the bed
помолюсь сейчас я тут просто на кровате
now
лежу сейчас
I
я
O found Yeah oh
О нашёл
put on the charger
Ага о поставил на зарядку
Yes yes there is Yes look it just turns out that's it for
Да да есть Да смотри просто получается
me Yes I wonder
вот мне Да интересно
uh Why don't you like over twenty
ээ Почему не хочешь типа старше двадцати
bird
пти
Well she she will decide my children like
Ну она она же будет решать моих детей
that And the field of bird is already difficult to
так А поле пти уже трудно
give birth and what Well that's it
рожать а что Ну вот
and from what age then for Zhaniya
так а от скольки тогда вот для Жания
children from what age is the best t Because
детей от скольки самое лучшее ть Потому
from 18 to to 2 p That is, in principle,
что от 18 до до 2 п То есть в принципе
for an eighteen-year-old would  got married yes And
на восемнадцатилетний бы женился да А
how many children does she want to give birth to so
сколько детей хочет чтобы она родила так
God will give Well yes Well what do you think is
Бог даст Ну да Ну вот как ты считаешь
normal for an
нормально для
Orthodox three four I have
православного трое четверо у меня
four just so
четверо как
yes but by the way my wife
раз так что да но у меня жена кстати
gave birth to her first at 27
родила первого в 27
Cool Yes and then so with an interval of
Прикольно Да и потом так с интервалом в
3 years That's how we
3 года Вот так мы чере
did it in a row I was also worried that well we
сделали Я тоже переживал что ну мы
got married on 26 I was worried in a hurry I say
женились 26 я переживал спешил говорю
come on let's do it we do it so that already
давай давай делаем делаем чтобы уже
because well it was too
потому что ну тебе
late for you God gave everything is normal
поздно сделали Бог дал всё нормально
Yes God willing and 18 years Well don't you think
Да дай Бог а 18 лет Ну Тебе не кажется
that 18 cm can be a pain gap
что 18 може см боль разрыв
33 gap yes And what other
33 разрыв да А какой нормальный ещё
gap is normal Well the least How much can be
разрыв вот Ну самое меньше Сколько ий
five Well 5 years gap can be
быть пять Ну 5 лет разрыв может быть
M 5 years gap can be Well so if 5
М 5 лет разрыв может быть Ну так если 5
years then that's already 20 she needs 28 so that it was
лет то это уже 20 ей нужно 28 чтобы было
and not 25
а не 25
even 28 is the maximum so you just
даже 28 - это максимум так ты просто вот
you said that the maximum is 25 now the
ты говорил что максимум 25 теперь
maximum is
максимум
28 This is not this at all in principle
28 Это не это вообще в принципе
listen to you I'm telling you And if this happens
слушай тебе я гово А если вот будет
because I know too We have a
такое потому что я знаю тоже У нас
story one priest He he up  40 years did
история один священник Он он до 40 лет
not get married kept asking God to send
не женился всё просил чтобы Бог послал
him a bride God sent him a bride 7
ему невесту ему послал Бог невесту на 7
years older than himself he was 40 she is 47 if
лет себя старше ему было 40 ей 47 если
God sends you you will be 33 And she is 40 you
тебе пошлёт Бог тебе будет 33 А ей 40
will accept her God forbid no so I mean so
примешь её не дай Бог нет так В смысле
if God
так это если Бог
sends no and why not he will not send no And
пошлёт нет а почему нет не пошлёт не А
how Well I just can not understand well
как Ну я просто не могу понять ну
Lins is our yesterday this one who
Линс это наш вчерашний этот что пиццу
ate pizza as soon as the conversation turns to
жрал как только заходит разговор за
some kind of relationship he has a gluttony asks
какие-то отношения у него жор просы
likes subscription comments and he is a sly
нается лайк подписка комент а он хитрый
bugger wants a young one And an
жук молоденькую хочет А
old one You look at yourself dude Who needs you
старую Ты на себя чувак посмотри Кому ты
anyway
вообще
letter on y Telegram right now axis
нужен пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
VN
ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through SRG ORV in your ban and very
нас через срг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational connection
того чтоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
write right now and while
пишиться прямо зараз а пок
there in telegrams okrim video also
там в телеграми окрим видео ще теж
interesting and useful information and we will oblige
цикава и корисна информация и мы повинни
you to keep constant operational
з вами тримати постийний оперативный
connection
звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe and
подпишись а